# Curriculum vitae

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

# Nancy Minyoi Mulozi

- Tommilantie 1b A 18 A, Pori (Finland)
- 358469500751
- minyoi2710@gmail.com
- Skype Nancy minyoi

#### PERSONAL STATEMENT

I'm a self-motivated disciplined professional offering strong communication and quick thinking skills, works effectively in team's as well as independently in fast-paced environments. I bring with me vast experience in Accounting, Marketing, and Sales and Banking.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### 01/06/2013-30/09/2016

# Relationship Manager

United Bank for Africa Zambia Ltd, Lusaka (Zambia)

- Aggressively market the bank's products to ensure favourable market response and optimum build-up of revenue.
- Drive collections in customer's accounts
- Ensure proper documentation throughput the credit application and process
- Sourcing for and monitoring of customer's tenured investment / facilities.
- Respond promptly and satisfactorily to customer's daily request and complaints.
- Prepare weekly and monthly statistics/performance reports for management use.
- Monitoring of the customer's main account regularly
- Reconcile all transactions on customer's accounts where and when necessary.
- Assist with the processing of customer's letters of credit and invisible transactions.
- Initiate and carry out recovery action on non-performing credits facilities
- Maintain comprehensive database of the customer's operational records including the existing and prospective customer data.
- E-Solutions Acquiring (POS, Internet Banking etc
- Perform other duties as assigned by the Head of Department

#### 03/01/2013-30/06/2013

## Sales representative

DHL International Zambia, lusaka (Zambia)

- Achieve sales and customer service objectives
- Selling services and increased the profit margin
- Planning sales strategies
- Performing all administrative tasks as per guidelines to account opening
- Working as a liaison between management and customers
- Play an important role in defining key market segments
- Conducting reference and background checks for the organization
- Manage clients' staffing requirements

Curriculum vitae Nancy Minyoi Mulozi

■ Developing business relations with industry contacts for providing best customer services

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

#### 06/02/2008-11/05/2012

# Bachelors of Business Administration - Honours, Banking and Finance

University of Namibia, windhoek (Namibia)

- Project Management
- \_ Marketing Management
- Management Accounting
- \_ Management Information Systems
- \_ Banking and Finance
- \_ statistics
- Basic ICT
- Macro Economics

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

#### Mother tongue(s)

#### English

## Other language(s)

UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
Listening	Reading	Spoken interaction	Spoken production	
A1	A1	A1		A1

Afrikaans

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user - B1 and B2: Independent user - C1 and C2: Proficient user Common European Framework of Reference for Languages

# Communication skills

- Good communication skills gained through experience as a Sales and Relationship Manger
- Impeccable command of written and oral English
- Able to interact with different nationalities

## Organisational / managerial skills

- Team Player
- Flexible
- Good organisational skills
- Self Solution driven

## Job-related skills

- Business development skills
- Good interactions with clients
- sound knowledge of Banking processes and procedures
- sales knowledge

# Digital competence

SELF-ASSESSMENT					
Information processing	Communication	Content creation	Safety	Problem solving	
Proficient user	Independent user	Basic user	Basic user	Basic user	

Curriculum vitae Nancy Minyoi Mulozi

## Digital competences - Self-assessment grid

#### **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

### References

Hulda Marisa

Branch Operations Manager
United bank For Africa Zambia Ltd
Stand 22768, Thabo Mbeki Road, Lusaka
Hulda.marisa@ubagroup.com
Cell:0977538391

Lombe Mbalashi

Legal Advisor

ZCCM-IH

P. O. Box 30048

lombem@justice.com

Lusaka

Cell: 0977725845 **Mr. Edwin Odero** 

Lecturer

Faculty of Economics and Management Science

University of Namibia

P/b 13301

Tell: 264 61 2063111

Edwins.odero@unam.na